<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Res App Full Code</string>

    <string-array name="authors">
        <item>Pick a Writer</item>
        <item>Oscar Wilde</item>
        <item>CS Lewis</item>
        <item>Bram Stoker</item>
        <item>Jonathan Swift</item>
        <item>Samuel Beckett</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="pickanauthor">Pick me a writer so I have something to read!!!</string>
    <string name="whoistheauthor">Who are you going to pick??</string>
    <string name="defaultquote">Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try again. Fail again. Fail better.
                                Try again. Fail again. Better again. Or better worse. Fail worse again.
                                Still worse again. Till sick for good. Throw up for good. Go for good.
                                Where neither for good. Good and all.
                                \n— Samuel Beckett</string>

    <string name="wildebook">The Picture of Dorian Gray (1890)</string>
    <string name="lewisbook">The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe (1950)</string>
    <string name="stokerbook">Dracula (1897)</string>
    <string name="swiftbook">Gullivers Travels (1726)</string>
    <string name="beckettbook">Waiting for Godot (1953)</string>

    <string name="wildequote">Those who find ugly meanings in beautiful things are corrupt without being charming.
                              This is a fault. Those who find beautiful meanings in beautiful things are the cultivated.
                              For these there is hope. They are the elect to whom beautiful things mean only Beauty</string>
    <string name="lewisquote">Logic! said the Professor half to himself. Why do they not teach logic at these schools?
                              There are only three possibilities. Either your sister is telling lies, or she is mad,
                              or she is telling the truth. You know she does not tell lies and it is obvious that she is
                              not mad. For the moment then and unless any further evidence turns up, we must assume that
                              she is telling the truth.</string>
    <string name="stokerquote">When the Count saw my face, his eyes blazed with a sort of demoniac fury, and he suddenly made
                               a grab at my throat. I drew away, and his hand touched the string of beads which held the crucifix.
                               It made an instant change in him, for the fury passed so quickly that I could hardly believe that
                               it was ever there.</string>
    <string name="swiftquote">This made me reflect how vain an attempt it is for a man to endeavor doing himself honor among
                              those who are out of all degree of equality or comparison with him. And yet I have seen the moral
                              of my own behavior very frequent in England since my return, where a little contemptible varlet,
                              without the least title to birth, person, wit, or common sense, shall presume to look with importance,
                              and put himself upon a foot with the greatest persons of the kingdom.</string>
    <string name="beckettquote">Have you not done tormenting me with your accursed time! It is abominable! When! When! One day, is
                                that not enough for you, one day he went dumb, one day I went blind, one day we will go deaf, one day
                                we were born, one day we shall die, the same day, the same second, is that not enough for you? They
                                give birth astride of a grave, the light gleams an instant, then it is night once more.</string>
    <string name="next" />
    <string name="hello_first_fragment" />
    <string name="previous" />
    <string name="action_settings" />
    <string name="first_fragment_label" />
    <string name="second_fragment_label" />

</resources>
